This site requires JavaScript. Please enable JavaScript by following [this link.](http://www.enable-javascript.com/ "Enable Javascript")

This site requires the use of cookies. Please enable cookies by following [this link.](http://www.wikihow.com/Enable-Cookies-in-Your-Internet-Web-Browser "Enable Cookies")

Menu

[Register](https://www.hbf.com.au/myhbf/register "Register") or [Login](https://www.hbf.com.au/myhbf/login "Login")

133 423

Type your search query  Submit your search

* [Health insurance](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance) Health insurance
    
    Health insurance
    
    * [Health cover](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance) Health cover
        
        Health cover

    * [Extras cover](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance/extras-insurance) Extras cover
        
        Extras cover

    * [Hospital cover](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance/hospital-insurance) Hospital cover
        
        Hospital cover

    * [Cover for...](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance) Cover for...
        
        Cover for...

* [Members](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Members
    
    Members
    
    * [Added benefits](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Added benefits
        
        Added benefits

    * [FAQs](https://www.hbf.com.au/members/hospital-guide/private-health-insurance-faqs-and-how-it-works) FAQs
        
        FAQs

    * [Member resources](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Member resources
        
        Member resources

    * [Handy tools](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Handy tools
        
        Handy tools

    * [Helpful articles](https://www.hbf.com.au/blog) Helpful articles
        
        Helpful articles

    How-to guides
    
    Check out our simple how-to guides to assist you in managing your HBF cover online, anytime.

Privacy
=======

See how HBF uses, manages, stores and discloses your personal information.

How we protect your information:
--------------------------------

We respect the privacy of your personal information.

* We process personal details on a daily basis and are committed to ensuring that the privacy and security of personal information remains protected.
* We are bound by the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) set out in the Privacy Act.

Privacy at HBF
--------------

The HBF Privacy Policy is a document which provides a comprehensive overview of how HBF handles the personal information it collects from those it interacts with, including HBF members, providers and the general public who may use the HBF website, participate in HBF events or obtain quotes.

The HBF Privacy Policy also includes information about how you can access and/or seek the correction of your personal information that we hold and make a complaint about the way your information is being handled by HBF and how HBF will deal with your complaint. You can view the [HBF Privacy Policy here.](https://www.hbf.com.au/about-hbf/legal/privacy-policy "HBF Privacy Policy here.")

A Collection Statement (also sometimes referred to as a Privacy Statement or Privacy Information) is directed specifically to the relationship you are entering into with HBF. For example when you purchase a health insurance product from HBF, we will provide you with a Private Health Insurance Collection Statement; if you are a participant in the HBF Run for a Reason you will have been provided with a Privacy Statement within the Terms of Entry that relates to how HBF manages your personal information for that event.

If you want to understand in detail how HBF will handle your personal information as a result of the purchase of an insurance product from HBF, as a result of entering an event that is run by HBF or where you have formed another relationship with HBF this page contains links to the Collection Statements that will have been provided to you on that purchase or on entering that relationship for your reference.

Please note that more than one Collection Statement may be relevant to you if you have entered into a variety of interactions with HBF. Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions.

* If you have a health insurance product with HBF you should refer to the [Private Health Insurance Collection Statement](https://www.hbf.com.au/-/media/files/about-us/legal/hbf-phi-collection-statement.pdf?la=en&hash=C0476BD06BB61F4362B710E87B4806254D6595F6 "opens in new window")
* If you are a medical provider you should refer to the [Providers / Health Practitioners Collection Statement](https://www.hbf.com.au/-/media/files/pdfs/provider-forms/hbf16089-provider-collection-statement.pdf?la=en&hash=46CCD9DB1C4973D92112F3B48343A4B5E971C06B "Providers / Health Practitioners Collection Statement")
* If you use our website or our HBF App you should refer to the Website and App Privacy Statement, contained in the [HBF Terms of Use](https://www.hbf.com.au/about-hbf/legal/terms-of-use "opens in new window")
* If you are enrolled into a Health Service program provided by HBF you should refer to the [HBF Health Service Programs Collection Statement](https://www.hbf.com.au/-/media/files/about-us/legal/hbf16144-health-programs-privacy-collection-statement.pdf?la=en&hash=7558BCA73FD4832FA2C9EE311A58031B8235EC9F "opens in new window")
* If you are a participant in the HBF Run for a Reason you should refer to the Privacy Information contained in the [Terms of Entry](https://www.hbfrun.com.au/terms-and-conditions/terms-of-entry "opens in new window")

As noted in HBF’s Privacy Policy and if applicable the Collection Statements, the countries where personal information about you may be disclosed to or accessed from in the course of HBF’s functions and activities are listed below. This list does not include countries where you may have specifically instructed HBF to send your information or expressly consented to HBF sending your information. HBF may also disclose or provide access to personal information about you to recipients in other countries from time to time that are not on this list, where HBF’s service providers or other third parties hold data or where their IT operations may be located.

* United States
* United Kingdom
* Canada
* India
* Singapore
* Germany
* Ireland
* Philippines

This list is updated from time to time. You can visit the HBF website at any time to view the latest version.

Please feel free to contact us if you have any further questions.

* #### About
    
* #### Contact
    
* #### Legal
    
* #### Search

###### Get the HBF app

© 2024 Copyright HBF Health Limited - (ABN) 11 126 884 786 and its subsidiaries.

Please select your state or territory
-------------------------------------

We need to confirm your location to show you the correct content, products and pricing.

Change your state or territory
------------------------------

If you change location, we'll reset your quote and refresh the page to show you the content, products and pricing relevant to your location.

Please select your state or territory
-------------------------------------

We need to confirm your location to show you the correct content, products and pricing.

Change your state or territory
------------------------------

If you change location, we'll reset your quote and refresh the page to show you the content, products and pricing relevant to your location.

Close

Type your search query 

* [Health insurance](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance) Health insurance
    
    Health insurance
    
    * [Health cover](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance) Health cover
        
        Health cover

    * [Extras cover](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance/extras-insurance) Extras cover
        
        Extras cover

    * [Hospital cover](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance/hospital-insurance) Hospital cover
        
        Hospital cover

    * [Cover for...](https://www.hbf.com.au/health-insurance) Cover for...
        
        Cover for...

* [Members](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Members
    
    Members
    
    * [Added benefits](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Added benefits
        
        Added benefits

    * [FAQs](https://www.hbf.com.au/members/hospital-guide/private-health-insurance-faqs-and-how-it-works) FAQs
        
        FAQs

    * [Member resources](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Member resources
        
        Member resources

    * [Handy tools](https://www.hbf.com.au/members) Handy tools
        
        Handy tools

    * [Helpful articles](https://www.hbf.com.au/blog) Helpful articles
        
        Helpful articles

    How-to guides
    
    Check out our simple how-to guides to assist you in managing your HBF cover online, anytime.
